<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<metadata>
	<idinfo>
		<citation>
			<citeinfo>
				<origin>Reitman, J.</origin>
				<origin>Rodriguez, B.D.</origin>
				<origin>Brown, P.J.</origin>								
				<pubdate>2020</pubdate>
				<title>{title}</title>
				<edition>1</edition>
				<geoform>ASCII and Binary Digital Data</geoform>
				<pubinfo>
					<pubplace>Denver, CO</pubplace>
					<publish>U.S. Geological Survey</publish>
				</pubinfo>
				<othercit>Additional information about Originators: Reitman, J., http://orcid.org/0000-0003-3551-9884; Rodriguez, B.D., http://orcid.org/0000-0002-2263-611X; Brown, P.J., http://orcid.org/0000-0002-2415-7462</othercit>
				<onlink>https://doi.org/10.5066/P91599D6</onlink>
			</citeinfo>
		</citation>
		<descript>
			<abstract>This dataset includes audio-magnetotelluric (AMT) sounding data collected in 2008 in and near the Patagonia Mountains of southern Arizona. The U.S. Geological Survey (USGS) conducted a series of multidisciplinary studies as part of the Assessment Techniques for Concealed Mineral Resources project funded by the USGS Minerals Resources Program in cooperation with the U.S. Forest Service. The USGS used AMT data at 6 sites along a southwest-northeast profile of about 10 kilometers across the northwest-trending Sunnyside porphyry copper system.</abstract>
			<purpose>The purpose of this data release is to provide audio-magnetotelluric (AMT) station locations and data to the public. The primary goal of the AMT survey is to map changes in electrical resistivity with depth that are related to differences in rock type. Characterization of the size and resistivity of the mineralized area beneath overburden were of primary importance to be investigated by these variations in rock types.</purpose>
			<supplinf>
				This data product contains MT transfer functions (TFs), which define the frequency-dependent linear relations between components of electromagnetic (EM) field variations measured at a single site. Two sorts of TF are provided for most sites. All TFs provide input data for subsequent MT inversion and interpretation. They are estimated from the raw EM time series by (a) Fourier transforming data in a series of short overlapping time windows, and (b) applying robust regression methods to the resulting sequence of Fourier coefficients. Remote reference stations were not used because manmade noise sources were assumed to be minimal in this remote area. Apparent resistivities and phases, which can be computed from the off-diagonal components of the impedance tensors, are frequently used in 2-dimensional (2D) interpretations. The EMTF data product includes estimates of the TFs for a range of periods (which may vary, depending on instrumentation and deployment time), as well as estimation error covariances.
				For more information on the EDI data format:
				Wight, David E., 1988, MT/EMAP Data Interchange Standard, Revision 1.0: Society of Exploration Geophysicists technical standards committee report, 77 p, isbn = 9780931830617, http://www.seg.org/documents/10161/77915/seg_mt_emap_1987.pdf. This report can be downloaded for free from the Society of Exploration Geophysics (SEG) Technical Standards website, http://seg.org/Publications/SEG-Technical-Standards. These metadata document the full suite of MT data for this site and includes the files below. Their contents are described in the entity and attribute section of the metadata.
 {BeginFileListingHere}
				</supplinf>
		</descript>
		<timeperd>
			<timeinfo>
				<rngdates>
					<begdate>{begdate}</begdate>
					<enddate>{enddate}</enddate>
				</rngdates>
			</timeinfo>
			<current>ground condition</current>
		</timeperd>
		<status>
			<progress>Complete</progress>
			<update>Not planned</update>
		</status>
		<spdom>
			<bounding>
				<westbc>{SiteLon}</westbc>
				<eastbc>{SiteLon}</eastbc>
				<northbc>{SiteLat}</northbc>
				<southbc>{SiteLat}</southbc>
			</bounding>
		</spdom>
 {keywords}
		<accconst>Please see 'Distribution Info' for details.</accconst>
		<useconst>There is no guarantee concerning the accuracy of the data. Any user who modifies the data is obligated to describe the types of modifications they perform. Data have been checked to ensure the accuracy. If any errors are detected, please notify the originating office. The U.S. Geological Survey strongly recommends that careful attention be paid to the metadata file associated with these data. Acknowledgment of the U.S. Geological Survey would be appreciated in products derived from these data. User specifically agrees not to misrepresent the data, nor to imply that changes made were approved or endorsed by the U.S. Geological Survey. Please refer to https://www2.usgs.gov/laws/privacy.html for the USGS disclaimer.</useconst>
		<ptcontac>
			<cntinfo>
				<cntorgp>
					<cntorg>U.S. Geological Survey</cntorg>
					<cntper>Brian D. Rodriguez</cntper>
				</cntorgp>
				<cntpos>Research Geophysicist</cntpos>
				<cntaddr>
					<addrtype>Physical</addrtype>
					<address>PO Box 25046</address>
					<city>Denver</city>
					<state>CO</state>
					<postal>80225-0046</postal>
					<country>US</country>
				</cntaddr>
				<cntvoice>303-236-1361</cntvoice>
				<cntemail>brod@usgs.gov</cntemail>
			</cntinfo>
		</ptcontac>
		<datacred>Data collected by Brian D. Rodriguez and Jay A. Sampson of the Geology, Geophysics and Geochemistry Science Center. This project was funded by U.S. Geological Survey (USGS) Minerals Resources Program (MRP).</datacred>
		<native>MS-DOS version 6.22</native>
	</idinfo>
	<dataqual>
		<attracc>
			<attraccr>The data have been peer reviewed and compared with related ancillary data.</attraccr>
		</attracc>
		<logic>Data were reviewed for consistency and analyses results were checked for validity.</logic>
		<complete>Data set is considered complete for the information presented, as described in the abstract. Users are advised to read the rest of the metadata record carefully for additional details. All magnetotelluric stations as part of this survey were included in this data release for the region and time period specified in this metadata.</complete>
		<posacc>
			<horizpa>
				<horizpar>Spatial locations were determined from hand-held global positioning system (GPS) devices. In general, the GPS units used by field scientists recorded sample locations to within 100 feet (30 meters) of the true location. The locations were verified using a geographic information system (GIS) and digital topographic maps.</horizpar>
			</horizpa>
			<vertacc>
				<vertaccr>Elevations were determined from The USGS National Map Bulk Point Query Service based on the USGS 3DEP (3D elevation program) 1/3 arc-second layer (10-meter). Vertical accuracy was not assessed for this specific dataset. The overall absolute vertical accuracy of the seamless DEMs within the conterminous United States (2013), expressed as the root mean square error (RMSE) of 25,310 reference points, was 1.55 meters (USGS, 2014 -  http://dx.doi.org/10.3133/ofr20141008). The vertical accuracy varies across the U.S. as a result of differences in source DEM quality, terrain relief, land cover, and other factors.</vertaccr>
			</vertacc>
		</posacc>
		<lineage>
			<procstep>
	        	<procdesc>Multiple high frequency time series (TS1 file extension), Fourier Coefficient (FC6, FC7, FC8, and FC9 file extensions), and Synchronous Detection Mode spectra cross power blocks (SD6, SD7, SD8, and SD9 file extensions) were each recorded for about 1 minute with an Electromagnetic Instruments (EMI) MT-1 MT data acquisition instrument employing orthogonal horizontal EMI AMT induction magnetic coils and EMI Titanium electrodes, along with a vertical EMI AMT induction magnetic coil. The proprietary, DOS-based, EMI recording software used is MTACQ, version 2.00 (September 17, 2004). The collected time series were stored on a portable field-rugged laptop computer and then converted to intermediate spectra cross power files (BP1 file extension) using fast Fourier transform (FFT) techniques and least-squares, cross-spectral analysis to solve for a tensor transfer function. Remote reference stations were not used because manmade noise sources were assumed to be minimal in this remote area. The time series and spectra cross power files were downloaded from the portable laptop each evening for further processing. The time series files are readable by other third-party software, such as Geosystem's WinGLink, version 2.20.02 (June 5, 2008), but the Fourier Coefficient and cross power files are only known to be readable by the EMI proprietary software.</procdesc>
				<procdate>{CollectionDate}</procdate>
			</procstep>
			<procstep>
				<procdesc>Combine multiple frequency band BP and SD cross power files into a single cross power file (AVG file extension) using EMI's MTACQ, version 2.00, software</procdesc>
				<procdate>{CombinationDate}</procdate>
			</procstep>
			<procstep>
				<procdesc>Convert cross power AVG file to spectra edi file using EMI's MTACQ, version 2.00, software</procdesc>
				<procdate>{ConversionDate}</procdate>
			</procstep>
			<procstep>
				<procdesc>Rotate data to geographic north and convert spectra edi file to a Transfer Function dump file using the proprietary, Windows-based, Geotools' GeotoolsMT, version 7.30 (May 28, 1998), software</procdesc>
				<procdate>{RotationDate}</procdate>
			</procstep>
			<procstep>
				<procdesc>Use EDITFMD File Conversion Utility, version 6.6 to extract survey and station information and settings from AVG, spectra edi, and dump files to create a Transfer Function edi file</procdesc>
				<procdate>{HarvestDate}</procdate>
			</procstep>
			<procstep>
				<procdesc>Use python tool, SquamataAssemblyAMTv1-13.ipynb, accessed at https://github.com/pbrown-usgs/SquamataAssemblyAMT, to extract survey and station information from AVG, spectra edi, and Transfer Function edi file to FGDC-compliant metadata.</procdesc>
				<procdate>20200311</procdate>
	</procstep>		</lineage>
	</dataqual>
	<spdoinfo>
		<direct>Point</direct>
		<ptvctinf>
			<sdtsterm>
				<sdtstype>Entity point</sdtstype>
				<ptvctcnt>1</ptvctcnt>
			</sdtsterm>
		</ptvctinf>
	</spdoinfo>
	<spref>
		<horizsys>
			<geograph>
				<latres>0.00001</latres>
				<longres>0.00001</longres>
				<geogunit>Decimal degrees</geogunit>
			</geograph>
			<geodetic>
				<horizdn>NAD27 CONUS</horizdn>
				<ellips>Clarke 1866</ellips>
				<semiaxis>6378206.4</semiaxis>
				<denflat>294.9786982</denflat>
			</geodetic>
		</horizsys>
	</spref>
	<eainfo>
		<detailed>
			<enttyp>
				<enttypl>Text File {EdiFileName}</enttypl>
				<enttypd>Transfer Function EDI File</enttypd>
				<enttypds>U.S. Geological Survey</enttypds>
			</enttyp>
			<attr>
				<attrlabl>HEAD</attrlabl>
				<attrdef>Header file information containing survey and station collection information.</attrdef>
				<attrdefs>U.S. Geological Survey</attrdefs>
				<attrdomv>
					<udom>Header block of information containing survey and station collection content, acquisition date, version, and software used to process.</udom>
				</attrdomv>
			</attr>
			<attr>
				<attrlabl>INFO</attrlabl>
				<attrdef>Descriptive content, or metadata, describing the data collection.</attrdef>
				<attrdefs>U.S. Geological Survey</attrdefs>
				<attrdomv>
					<udom>Descriptive content, or metadata, describing the data collection including abstract, data description, instrumentation with equipment identifiers, notes, data collection and processing details including software and other contextual information.</udom>
				</attrdomv>
			</attr>
			<attr>
				<attrlabl>FREQ</attrlabl>
				<attrdef>Data block containing a set of frequencies in hertz (Hz.) It defines the frequency set for succeeding data within that data section which are functions of frequency.</attrdef>
				<attrdefs>U.S. Geological Survey</attrdefs>
				<attrdomv>
				<rdom>
				<rdommin>{frequencyMin}</rdommin>
				<rdommax>{frequencyMax}</rdommax>
				<attrunit>Hertz</attrunit>
			</rdom>
			</attrdomv>
			</attr>
			<attr>
				<attrlabl>ZROT</attrlabl>
				<attrdef>Data block containing a set of rotation angles in degrees used for impedances.</attrdef>
				<attrdefs>U.S. Geological Survey</attrdefs>
				<attrdomv>
				<rdom>
				<rdommin>{rotationMin}</rdommin>
				<rdommax>{rotationMax}</rdommax>
				<attrunit>Degrees</attrunit>
				</rdom>
				</attrdomv>
			</attr>
			{ImpedanceAttributes}
			{TipperAttributes}
			<attr>
				<attrlabl>RHOROT</attrlabl>
				<attrdef>Data block containing a set of rotation angles in degrees used for apparent resistivities.</attrdef>
				<attrdefs>U.S. Geological Survey</attrdefs>
				<attrdomv>
					<rdom>
				<rdommin>{RHOROTmin}</rdommin>
				<rdommax>{RHOROTmax}</rdommax>
				<attrunit>Degrees</attrunit>
				</rdom>
				</attrdomv>
			</attr>
			<attr>
				<attrlabl>RHOXX</attrlabl>
				<attrdef>Magnitude of apparent resistivity (ohm-m) computed from Zxx</attrdef>
				<attrdefs>U.S. Geological Survey</attrdefs>
				<attrdomv>
					<rdom>
				<rdommin>{RHOXXmin}</rdommin>
				<rdommax>{RHOXXmax}</rdommax>
				<attrunit>ohm-m</attrunit>
				</rdom>
				</attrdomv>
			</attr>
			<attr>
				<attrlabl>RHOXX.ERR</attrlabl>
				<attrdef>Log10 error bar (in decades) associated with Rhoxx</attrdef>
				<attrdefs>U.S. Geological Survey</attrdefs>
				<attrdomv>
					<rdom>
				<rdommin>{RHOXXERRmin}</rdommin>
				<rdommax>{RHOXXERRmax}</rdommax>
				<attrunit>Log10 ohm-m</attrunit>
				</rdom>
				</attrdomv>
			</attr>
			<attr>
				<attrlabl>RHOXY</attrlabl>
				<attrdef>Magnitude of apparent resistivity (ohm-m) computed from Zxy</attrdef>
				<attrdefs>U.S. Geological Survey</attrdefs>
				<attrdomv>
					<rdom>
				<rdommin>{RHOXYmin}</rdommin>
				<rdommax>{RHOXYmax}</rdommax>
				<attrunit>ohm-m</attrunit>
				</rdom>
				</attrdomv>
			</attr>
			<attr>
				<attrlabl>RHOXY.ERR</attrlabl>
				<attrdef>Log10 error bar (in decades) associated with Rhoxy</attrdef>
				<attrdefs>U.S. Geological Survey</attrdefs>
				<attrdomv>
					<rdom>
				<rdommin>{RHOXYERRmin}</rdommin>
				<rdommax>{RHOXYERRmax}</rdommax>
				<attrunit>Log10 ohm-m</attrunit>
				</rdom>
				</attrdomv>
			</attr>
			<attr>
				<attrlabl>RHOYX</attrlabl>
				<attrdef>Magnitude of apparent resistivity (ohm-m) computed from Zyx</attrdef>
				<attrdefs>U.S. Geological Survey</attrdefs>
				<attrdomv>
					<rdom>
				<rdommin>{RHOYXmin}</rdommin>
				<rdommax>{RHOYXmax}</rdommax>
				<attrunit>ohm-m</attrunit>
				</rdom>
				</attrdomv>
			</attr>
			<attr>
				<attrlabl>RHOYX.ERR</attrlabl>
				<attrdef>Log10 error bar (in decades) associated with Rhoyx</attrdef>
				<attrdefs>U.S. Geological Survey</attrdefs>
				<attrdomv>
					<rdom>
				<rdommin>{RHOYXERRmin}</rdommin>
				<rdommax>{RHOYXERRmax}</rdommax>
				<attrunit>Log10 ohm-m</attrunit>
				</rdom>
				</attrdomv>
			</attr>
			<attr>
				<attrlabl>RHOYY</attrlabl>
				<attrdef>Magnitude of apparent resistivity (ohm-m) computed from Zyy</attrdef>
				<attrdefs>U.S. Geological Survey</attrdefs>
				<attrdomv>
					<rdom>
				<rdommin>{RHOYYmin}</rdommin>
				<rdommax>{RHOYYmax}</rdommax>
				<attrunit>ohm-m</attrunit>
				</rdom>
				</attrdomv>
			</attr>
			<attr>
				<attrlabl>RHOYY.ERR</attrlabl>
				<attrdef>Log10 error bar (in decades) associated with Rhoyy</attrdef>
				<attrdefs>U.S. Geological Survey</attrdefs>
				<attrdomv>
					<rdom>
				<rdommin>{RHOYYERRmin}</rdommin>
				<rdommax>{RHOYYERRmax}</rdommax>
				<attrunit>Log10 ohm-m</attrunit>
				</rdom>
				</attrdomv>
			</attr>
			<attr>
				<attrlabl>PHSXX</attrlabl>
				<attrdef>Phase angle of apparent resistivity (deg) computed from Zxx</attrdef>
				<attrdefs>U.S. Geological Survey</attrdefs>
				<attrdomv>
					<rdom>
				<rdommin>{PHSXXmin}</rdommin>
				<rdommax>{PHSXXmax}</rdommax>
				<attrunit>Degrees</attrunit>
				</rdom>
				</attrdomv>
			</attr>
			<attr>
				<attrlabl>PHSXX.ERR</attrlabl>
				<attrdef>Error bar (in degrees) associated with Phsxx</attrdef>
				<attrdefs>U.S. Geological Survey</attrdefs>
				<attrdomv>
					<rdom>
				<rdommin>{PHSXXERRmin}</rdommin>
				<rdommax>{PHSXXERRmax}</rdommax>
				<attrunit>Degrees</attrunit>
				</rdom>
				</attrdomv>
			</attr>
			<attr>
				<attrlabl>PHSXY</attrlabl>
				<attrdef>Phase angle of apparent resistivity (deg) computed from Zxy</attrdef>
				<attrdefs>U.S. Geological Survey</attrdefs>
				<attrdomv>
					<rdom>
				<rdommin>{PHSXYmin}</rdommin>
				<rdommax>{PHSXYmax}</rdommax>
				<attrunit>Degrees</attrunit>
				</rdom>
				</attrdomv>
			</attr>
			<attr>
				<attrlabl>PHSXY.ERR</attrlabl>
				<attrdef>Error bar (in degrees) associated with Phsxy</attrdef>
				<attrdefs>U.S. Geological Survey</attrdefs>
				<attrdomv>
					<rdom>
				<rdommin>{PHSXYERRmin}</rdommin>
				<rdommax>{PHSXYERRmax}</rdommax>
				<attrunit>Degrees</attrunit>
				</rdom>
				</attrdomv>
			</attr>
			<attr>
				<attrlabl>PHSYX</attrlabl>
				<attrdef>Phase angle of apparent resistivity (deg) computed from Zyx</attrdef>
				<attrdefs>U.S. Geological Survey</attrdefs>
				<attrdomv>
					<rdom>
				<rdommin>{PHSYXmin}</rdommin>
				<rdommax>{PHSYXmax}</rdommax>
				<attrunit>Degrees</attrunit>
				</rdom>
				</attrdomv>
			</attr>
			<attr>
				<attrlabl>PHSYX.ERR</attrlabl>
				<attrdef>Error bar (in degrees) associated with Phsyx</attrdef>
				<attrdefs>U.S. Geological Survey</attrdefs>
				<attrdomv>
					<rdom>
				<rdommin>{PHSYXERRmin}</rdommin>
				<rdommax>{PHSYXERRmax}</rdommax>
				<attrunit>Degrees</attrunit>
				</rdom>
				</attrdomv>
			</attr>
			<attr>
				<attrlabl>PHSYY</attrlabl>
				<attrdef>Phase angle of apparent resistivity (deg) computed from Zyy</attrdef>
				<attrdefs>U.S. Geological Survey</attrdefs>
				<attrdomv>
					<rdom>
				<rdommin>{PHSYYmin}</rdommin>
				<rdommax>{PHSYYmax}</rdommax>
				<attrunit>Degrees</attrunit>
				</rdom>
				</attrdomv>
			</attr>
			<attr>
				<attrlabl>PHSYY.ERR</attrlabl>
				<attrdef>Error bar (in degrees) associated with Phsyy</attrdef>
				<attrdefs>U.S. Geological Survey</attrdefs>
				<attrdomv>
					<rdom>
				<rdommin>{PHSYYERRmin}</rdommin>
				<rdommax>{PHSYYERRmax}</rdommax>
				<attrunit>Degrees</attrunit>
				</rdom>
				</attrdomv>
			</attr>
			<attr>
				<attrlabl>TIPMAG</attrlabl>
				<attrdef>Magnitude of total tipper</attrdef>
				<attrdefs>U.S. Geological Survey</attrdefs>
				<attrdomv>
					<rdom>
				<rdommin>{TIPMAGmin}</rdommin>
				<rdommax>{TIPMAGmax}</rdommax>
				<attrunit>Unitless</attrunit>
				</rdom>
				</attrdomv>
			</attr>
			<attr>
				<attrlabl>TIPMAG.ERR</attrlabl>
				<attrdef>Error bar associated with TIPMAG</attrdef>
				<attrdefs>U.S. Geological Survey</attrdefs>
				<attrdomv>
					<rdom>
				<rdommin>{TIPMAGERRmin}</rdommin>
				<rdommax>{TIPMAGERRmax}</rdommax>
				<attrunit>Unitless</attrunit>
				</rdom>
				</attrdomv>
			</attr>
			<attr>
				<attrlabl>TIPPHS</attrlabl>
				<attrdef>Phase angle (deg) of total tipper</attrdef>
				<attrdefs>U.S. Geological Survey</attrdefs>
				<attrdomv>
					<rdom>
				<rdommin>{TIPPHSmin}</rdommin>
				<rdommax>{TIPPHSmax}</rdommax>
				<attrunit>Degrees</attrunit>
				</rdom>
				</attrdomv>
			</attr>
			<attr>
				<attrlabl>TIPPHS.ERR</attrlabl>
				<attrdef>Error bar (in degrees) associated with TIPPHS</attrdef>
				<attrdefs>U.S. Geological Survey</attrdefs>
				<attrdomv>
					<rdom>
				<rdommin>{TIPPHSERRmin}</rdommin>
				<rdommax>{TIPPHSERRmax}</rdommax>
				<attrunit>Degrees</attrunit>
				</rdom>
				</attrdomv>
			</attr>
			<attr>
				<attrlabl>ZSTRIKE</attrlabl>
				<attrdef>Impedance strike angle (deg) computed from the impedance tensor Z</attrdef>
				<attrdefs>U.S. Geological Survey</attrdefs>
				<attrdomv>
					<rdom>
				<rdommin>{ZSTRIKEmin}</rdommin>
				<rdommax>{ZSTRIKEmax}</rdommax>
				<attrunit>Degrees</attrunit>
				</rdom>
				</attrdomv>
			</attr>
			<attr>
				<attrlabl>ZSKEW</attrlabl>
				<attrdef>Impedance skew computed from the impedance tensor Z</attrdef>
				<attrdefs>U.S. Geological Survey</attrdefs>
				<attrdomv>
					<rdom>
				<rdommin>{ZSKEWmin}</rdommin>
				<rdommax>{ZSKEWmax}</rdommax>
				<attrunit>Unitless</attrunit>
				</rdom>
				</attrdomv>
			</attr>
			<attr>
				<attrlabl>TSTRIKE</attrlabl>
				<attrdef>Tipper strike angle (deg) computed from the tipper tensor T</attrdef>
				<attrdefs>U.S. Geological Survey</attrdefs>
				<attrdomv>
					<rdom>
				<rdommin>{TSTRIKEmin}</rdommin>
				<rdommax>{TSTRIKEmax}</rdommax>
				<attrunit>Degrees</attrunit>
				</rdom>
				</attrdomv>
			</attr>
			<attr>
				<attrlabl>COH MEAS1=1011.001  MEAS2=1015.001</attrlabl>
				<attrdef>Ordinary coherency between any two measurements as a function of freq.</attrdef>
				<attrdefs>U.S. Geological Survey</attrdefs>
				<attrdomv>
					<rdom>
				<rdommin>{COH1min}</rdommin>
				<rdommax>{COH1max}</rdommax>
				<attrunit>Unitless</attrunit>
				</rdom>
				</attrdomv>
			</attr>
			<attr>
				<attrlabl>COH MEAS1=1012.001  MEAS2=1014.001</attrlabl>
				<attrdef>Ordinary coherency between any two measurements as a function of freq.</attrdef>
				<attrdefs>U.S. Geological Survey</attrdefs>
				<attrdomv>
					<rdom>
				<rdommin>{COH2min}</rdommin>
				<rdommax>{COH2max}</rdommax>
				<attrunit>Unitless</attrunit>
				</rdom>
				</attrdomv>
			</attr>
			<attr>
				<attrlabl>COH MEAS1=1011.001  MEAS2=1014.001</attrlabl>
				<attrdef>Ordinary coherency between any two measurements as a function of freq.</attrdef>
				<attrdefs>U.S. Geological Survey</attrdefs>
				<attrdomv>
					<rdom>
				<rdommin>{COH3min}</rdommin>
				<rdommax>{COH3max}</rdommax>
				<attrunit>Unitless</attrunit>
				</rdom>
				</attrdomv>
			</attr>
			<attr>
				<attrlabl>COH MEAS1=1012.001  MEAS2=1015.001</attrlabl>
				<attrdef>Ordinary coherency between any two measurements as a function of freq.</attrdef>
				<attrdefs>U.S. Geological Survey</attrdefs>
				<attrdomv>
					<rdom>
				<rdommin>{COH4min}</rdommin>
				<rdommax>{COH4max}</rdommax>
				<attrunit>Unitless</attrunit>
				</rdom>
				</attrdomv>
			</attr>
			<attr>
				<attrlabl>EPREDCOH MEAS1=1011.001  MEAS2=1012.001  EPRED= 1014.001</attrlabl>
				<attrdef>Multiple coherency relationship between an E measurement, and a predicted E measurement derived from two H measurements and a tensor impedance Z.</attrdef>
				<attrdefs>U.S. Geological Survey</attrdefs>
				<attrdomv>
					<rdom>
				<rdommin>{EPREDCOH1min}</rdommin>
				<rdommax>{EPREDCOH1max}</rdommax>
				<attrunit>Unitless</attrunit>
				</rdom>
				</attrdomv>
			</attr>
			<attr>
				<attrlabl>EPREDCOH MEAS1=1011.001  MEAS2=1012.001  EPRED= 1015.001</attrlabl>
				<attrdef>Multiple coherency relationship between an E measurement, and a predicted E measurement derived from two H measurements and a tensor impedance Z.</attrdef>
				<attrdefs>U.S. Geological Survey</attrdefs>
				<attrdomv>
					<rdom>
				<rdommin>{EPREDCOH2min}</rdommin>
				<rdommax>{EPREDCOH2max}</rdommax>
				<attrunit>Unitless</attrunit>
				</rdom>
				</attrdomv>
			</attr>
			<attr>
				<attrlabl>SIGAMP  MEAS=1011</attrlabl>
				<attrdef>Signal amplitude (or power) spectra for a measurement as a function of frequency.</attrdef>
				<attrdefs>U.S. Geological Survey</attrdefs>
				<attrdomv>
					<rdom>
				<rdommin>{SIGAMP1min}</rdommin>
				<rdommax>{SIGAMP1max}</rdommax>
				<attrunit>gammas/SQRT(Hertz)</attrunit>
				</rdom>
				</attrdomv>
			</attr>
			<attr>
				<attrlabl>SIGAMP  MEAS=1012</attrlabl>
				<attrdef>Signal amplitude (or power) spectra for a measurement as a function of frequency.</attrdef>
				<attrdefs>U.S. Geological Survey</attrdefs>
				<attrdomv>
					<rdom>
				<rdommin>{SIGAMP2min}</rdommin>
				<rdommax>{SIGAMP2max}</rdommax>
				<attrunit>gammas/SQRT(Hertz)</attrunit>
				</rdom>
				</attrdomv>
			</attr>
			<attr>
				<attrlabl>SIGAMP  MEAS=1013</attrlabl>
				<attrdef>Signal amplitude (or power) spectra for a measurement as a function of frequency.</attrdef>
				<attrdefs>U.S. Geological Survey</attrdefs>
				<attrdomv>
					<rdom>
				<rdommin>{SIGAMP3min}</rdommin>
				<rdommax>{SIGAMP3max}</rdommax>
				<attrunit>gammas/SQRT(Hertz)</attrunit>
				</rdom>
				</attrdomv>
			</attr>
			<attr>
				<attrlabl>SIGAMP  MEAS=1014</attrlabl>
				<attrdef>Signal amplitude (or power) spectra for a measurement as a function of frequency.</attrdef>
				<attrdefs>U.S. Geological Survey</attrdefs>
				<attrdomv>
					<rdom>
				<rdommin>{SIGAMP4min}</rdommin>
				<rdommax>{SIGAMP4max}</rdommax>
				<attrunit>mV/Km/SQRT(Hertz)</attrunit>
				</rdom>
				</attrdomv>
			</attr>
			<attr>
				<attrlabl>SIGAMP  MEAS=1015</attrlabl>
				<attrdef>Signal amplitude (or power) spectra for a measurement as a function of frequency.</attrdef>
				<attrdefs>U.S. Geological Survey</attrdefs>
				<attrdomv>
					<rdom>
				<rdommin>{SIGAMP5min}</rdommin>
				<rdommax>{SIGAMP5max}</rdommax>
				<attrunit>mV/Km/SQRT(Hertz)</attrunit>
				</rdom>
				</attrdomv>
			</attr>
			<attr>
				<attrlabl>SIGNOISE MEAS=1011.001</attrlabl>
				<attrdef>Signal-to-noise ratio for a measurement as a function of frequency.</attrdef>
				<attrdefs>U.S. Geological Survey</attrdefs>
				<attrdomv>
					<rdom>
				<rdommin>{SIGNOISE1min}</rdommin>
				<rdommax>{SIGNOISE1max}</rdommax>
				<attrunit>Unitless</attrunit>
				</rdom>
				</attrdomv>
			</attr>
			<attr>
				<attrlabl>SIGNOISE MEAS=1012.001</attrlabl>
				<attrdef>Signal-to-noise ratio for a measurement as a function of frequency.</attrdef>
				<attrdefs>U.S. Geological Survey</attrdefs>
				<attrdomv>
					<rdom>
				<rdommin>{SIGNOISE2min}</rdommin>
				<rdommax>{SIGNOISE2max}</rdommax>
				<attrunit>Unitless</attrunit>
				</rdom>
				</attrdomv>
			</attr>
			<attr>
				<attrlabl>SIGNOISE MEAS=1013.001</attrlabl>
				<attrdef>Signal-to-noise ratio for a measurement as a function of frequency.</attrdef>
				<attrdefs>U.S. Geological Survey</attrdefs>
				<attrdomv>
					<rdom>
				<rdommin>{SIGNOISE3min}</rdommin>
				<rdommax>{SIGNOISE3max}</rdommax>
				<attrunit>Unitless</attrunit>
				</rdom>
				</attrdomv>
			</attr>
			<attr>
				<attrlabl>SIGNOISE MEAS=1014.001</attrlabl>
				<attrdef>Signal-to-noise ratio for a measurement as a function of frequency.</attrdef>
				<attrdefs>U.S. Geological Survey</attrdefs>
				<attrdomv>
					<rdom>
				<rdommin>{SIGNOISE4min}</rdommin>
				<rdommax>{SIGNOISE4max}</rdommax>
				<attrunit>Unitless</attrunit>
				</rdom>
				</attrdomv>
			</attr>
			<attr>
				<attrlabl>SIGNOISE MEAS=1015.001</attrlabl>
				<attrdef>Signal-to-noise ratio for a measurement as a function of frequency.</attrdef>
				<attrdefs>U.S. Geological Survey</attrdefs>
				<attrdomv>
					<rdom>
				<rdommin>{SIGNOISE5min}</rdommin>
				<rdommax>{SIGNOISE5max}</rdommax>
				<attrunit>Unitless</attrunit>
				</rdom>
				</attrdomv>
			</attr>
		</detailed>
	{EandA}
		<overview>
			<eaover>MT/EMAP Data Interchange Standard, Revision 1.0, Dec 1987, David E. Wight. This standard was never published in Geophysics.</eaover>
			<eadetcit>For more information on the EDI data format: Wight, D.E., 1988, MT/EMAP Data Interchange Standard, Technical standards committee report, Society of Exploration Geophysicists, isbn=9780931830617, http://www.seg.org/documents/10161/77915/seg_mt_emap_1987.pdf</eadetcit>
		</overview>
	</eainfo>
	<distinfo>
		<distrib>
			<cntinfo>
				<cntorgp>
					<cntorg>ScienceBase</cntorg>
					<cntper>U.S. Geological Survey</cntper>
				</cntorgp>
				<cntaddr>
					<addrtype>mailing and physical</addrtype>
					<address>Denver Federal Center, Building 810, Mail Stop 302</address>
					<city>Denver</city>
					<state>CO</state>
					<postal>80225</postal>
					<country>USA</country>
				</cntaddr>
				<cntvoice>1-888-275-8747</cntvoice>
				<cntemail>sciencebase@usgs.gov</cntemail>
			</cntinfo>
		</distrib>
		<distliab>Unless otherwise stated, all data, metadata and related materials are considered to satisfy the quality standards relative to the purpose for which the data were collected. Although these data and associated metadata have been reviewed for accuracy and completeness and approved for release by the U.S. Geological Survey (USGS), no warranty expressed or implied is made regarding the display or utility of the data for other purposes, nor on all computer systems, nor shall the act of distribution constitute any such warranty.</distliab>
	</distinfo>
	<metainfo>
		<metd>20200311</metd>
		<metc>
			<cntinfo>
				<cntperp>
					<cntper>Philip Brown</cntper>
					<cntorg>U.S. Geological Survey</cntorg>
				</cntperp>
				<cntpos>Geophysicist</cntpos>
				<cntaddr>
					<addrtype>Physical</addrtype>
					<address>PO Box 25046</address>
					<city>Denver</city>
					<state>CO</state>
					<postal>80225-0046</postal>
					<country>US</country>
				</cntaddr>
				<cntvoice>303-236-1310</cntvoice>
				<cntemail>pbrown@usgs.gov</cntemail>
				<cntinst>Additional information about metadata creator: Brown, P.J., http://orcid.org/0000-0002-2415-7462</cntinst>
			</cntinfo>
		</metc>
		<metstdn>FGDC Content Standard for Digital Geospatial Metadata</metstdn>
		<metstdv>FGDC-STD-001-1998</metstdv>
	</metainfo>
</metadata>
