<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<metadata>
	<idinfo>
		<citation>
			<citeinfo>
				<origin>Rodriguez, B. D.</origin>
				<origin>Brown, P. J.</origin>
				<origin>Hudson, M. R.</origin>
				<pubdate>2018</pubdate>
				<title>{title}</title>
				<edition>1</edition>
				<geoform>ASCII and Binary Digital Data</geoform>
				<pubinfo>
					<pubplace>Denver, CO</pubplace>
					<publish>U.S. Geological Survey</publish>
				</pubinfo>
				<othercit>Additional information about Originators:Rodriguez, B.D., http://orcid.org/0000-0002-2263-611X; Brown, P.J., http://orcid.org/0000-0002-2415-7462</othercit>
				<onlink>https://doi.org/10.5066/P9CIAXC5</onlink>
			</citeinfo>
		</citation>
		<descript>
			<abstract>This dataset includes audio-magnetotelluric (AMT) sounding data collected in August 2017 in the Buffalo River watershed of northern Arkansas by the U.S. Geological Survey (USGS). Along with geologic mapping, the USGS used AMT data at 6 sites along a southwest-northeast profile of about 7 kilometers across the inferred northeastern margin of the Bear Creek uplift within the southern Ozark Dome to better constrain the buried, northeastern margin of the Bear Creek uplift.</abstract>
			<purpose>The purpose of this data release is to provide audio-magnetotelluric (AMT) station locations and data to the public. The primary goal of the AMT survey is to map changes in electrical resistivity with depth that are related to differences in rock type. Characterization of buried aquifers and aquitards were of primary importance to be investigated by these variations in rock types.</purpose>
			<supplinf>
				This data product contains MT transfer functions (TFs), which define the frequency-dependent linear relations between components of electromagnetic (EM) field variations measured at a single site. Two sorts of TF are provided for most sites. All TFs provide input data for subsequent MT inversion and interpretation. They are estimated from the raw EM time series by (a) Fourier transforming data in a series of short overlapping time windows, and (b) applying robust regression methods to the resulting sequence of Fourier coefficients. For remote reference estimates data from a second site are used for noise cancellation, and to reduce bias due to noise in the predicting magnetic channels. Apparent resistivities and phases, which can be computed from the off-diagonal components of the impedance tensors, are frequently used in 2-dimensional (2D) interpretations. The EMTF data product includes estimates of the TFs for a range of periods (which may vary, depending on instrumentation and deployment time), as well as estimation error covariances.
				For more information on the EDI data format:
				Wight, David E., 1988, MT/EMAP Data Interchange Standard, Revision 1.0: Society of Exploration Geophysicists technical standards committee report, 77 p, isbn = 9780931830617, http://www.seg.org/documents/10161/77915/seg_mt_emap_1987.pdf. This report can be downloaded for free from the Society of Exploration Geophysics (SEG) Technical Standards website, http://seg.org/Publications/SEG-Technical-Standards. These metadata document the full suite of MT data for this site and includes the files below. Their contents are described in the entity and attribute section of the metadata.
				{BeginFileListingHere}
				</supplinf>
		</descript>
		<timeperd>
			<timeinfo>
				<rngdates>
					<begdate>{begdate}</begdate>
					<enddate>{enddate}</enddate>
				</rngdates>
			</timeinfo>
			<current>ground condition</current>
		</timeperd>
		<status>
			<progress>Complete</progress>
			<update>Not planned</update>
		</status>
		<spdom>
			<bounding>
				<westbc>{SiteLon}</westbc>
				<eastbc>{SiteLon}</eastbc>
				<northbc>{SiteLat}</northbc>
				<southbc>{SiteLat}</southbc>
			</bounding>
		</spdom>
 {keywords}
		<accconst>Please see 'Distribution Info' for details.</accconst>
		<useconst>There is no guarantee concerning the accuracy of the data. Any user who modifies the data is obligated to describe the types of modifications they perform. Data have been checked to ensure the accuracy. If any errors are detected, please notify the originating office. The U.S. Geological Survey strongly recommends that careful attention be paid to the metadata file associated with these data. Acknowledgment of the U.S. Geological Survey would be appreciated in products derived from these data. User specifically agrees not to misrepresent the data, nor to imply that changes made were approved or endorsed by the U.S. Geological Survey. Please refer to https://www2.usgs.gov/laws/privacy.html for the USGS disclaimer.</useconst>
		<ptcontac>
			<cntinfo>
				<cntorgp>
					<cntorg>USGS - Crustal Geophysics and Geochemistry Science Center</cntorg>
					<cntper>Brian D. Rodriguez</cntper>
				</cntorgp>
				<cntpos>Research Geophysicist</cntpos>
				<cntaddr>
					<addrtype>Physical</addrtype>
					<address>Mail Stop 964, West 6th Ave. and Kipling St., DFC Bldg. 20</address>
					<city>Denver</city>
					<state>CO</state>
					<postal>80225-0046</postal>
					<country>US</country>
				</cntaddr>
				<cntvoice>303-236-1361</cntvoice>
				<cntemail>brod@usgs.gov</cntemail>
			</cntinfo>
		</ptcontac>
		<datacred>Data collected by Brian D. Rodriguez and Mark R. Hudson of the Geology, Geophysics and Geochemistry Science Center. This project was funded by U.S. Geological Survey (USGS) Minerals Resources Program (MRP).</datacred>
		<native>MS-DOS version 6.22</native>
	</idinfo>
	<dataqual>
		<attracc>
			<attraccr>MS-DOS version 6.22</attraccr>
		</attracc>
		<logic>Data set is considered complete for the information presented, as described in the abstract. Users are advised to read the rest of the metadata record carefully for additional details.</logic>
		<complete>Data set is considered complete for the information presented, as described in the abstract. Users are advised to read the rest of the metadata record carefully for additional details.</complete>
		<posacc>
			<horizpa>
				<horizpar>Spatial locations were determined from hand-held global positioning system (GPS) devices. In general, the GPS units used by field scientists recorded sample locations to within 100 feet (30 meters) of the true location. The locations were verified using a geographic information system (GIS) and digital topographic maps.</horizpar>
			</horizpa>
			<vertacc>
				<vertaccr>Elevations were determined from USGS, The National Map, Bulk Point Query Service based on the USGS 3DEP (3D elevation program) 1/3 arc-second layer (10-meter). Vertical accuracy was not assessed for this specific dataset. The overall absolute vertical accuracy of the seamless DEMs within the conterminous United States (2013), expressed as the root mean square error (RMSE) of 25,310 reference points, was 1.55 meters (USGS, 2014 -  http://dx.doi.org/10.3133/ofr20141008). The vertical accuracy varies across the U.S. as a result of differences in source DEM quality, terrain relief, land cover, and other factors.</vertaccr>
			</vertacc>
		</posacc>
		<lineage>
			<procstep>
				<procdesc>Acquire multiple high frequency time series files (TS1 file extension) and convert to intermediate spectra cross power files (BP1 file extension)</procdesc>
				<procdate>20030709</procdate>
			</procstep>
			<procstep>
				<procdesc>Acquire multiple mid frequency time series files (TS2 file extension) and convert to intermediate spectra cross power files (BP2 file extension)</procdesc>
				<procdate>20030709</procdate>
			</procstep>
			<procstep>
				<procdesc>Acquire multiple low frequency time series files (TS3 file extension) and convert to intermediate spectra cross power files (BP3 file extension)</procdesc>
				<procdate>20030709</procdate>
			</procstep>
			<procstep>
				<procdesc>Combine multiple frequency band (high, mid, low) BP cross power files into a single cross power file (AVG file extension)</procdesc>
				<procdate>19800104</procdate>
			</procstep>
			<procstep>
				<procdesc>Convert cross power AVG file to spectra edi file</procdesc>
				<procdate>20171010</procdate>
			</procstep>
			<procstep>
				<procdesc>Rotate data to geographic north and convert spectra edi file to GeotoolsMT Transfer Function dump file</procdesc>
				<procdate>20171010</procdate>
			</procstep>
			<procstep>
				<procdesc>Mine AVG, spectra edi, and dump file to create Transfer Function edi file</procdesc>
				<procdate>20171023</procdate>
			</procstep>
		</lineage>
	</dataqual>
	<spdoinfo>
		<direct>Point</direct>
		<ptvctinf>
			<sdtsterm>
				<sdtstype>Entity point</sdtstype>
				<ptvctcnt>1</ptvctcnt>
			</sdtsterm>
		</ptvctinf>
	</spdoinfo>
	<spref>
		<horizsys>
			<geograph>
				<latres>0.0196481178</latres>
				<longres>0.0409100603</longres>
				<geogunit>Decimal degrees</geogunit>
			</geograph>
			<geodetic>
				<horizdn>NAD27 CONUS</horizdn>
				<ellips>Clarke 1866</ellips>
				<semiaxis>6378206.4</semiaxis>
				<denflat>294.9786982</denflat>
			</geodetic>
		</horizsys>
	</spref>
	{EandA}
		<overview>
			<eaover>MT/EMAP Data Interchange Standard, Revision 1.0, Dec 1987, David E. Wight. This standard was never published in Geophysics.</eaover>
			<eadetcit>For more information on the EDI data format: Wight, D.E., 1988, MT/EMAP Data Interchange Standard, Technical standards committee report, Society of Exploration Geophysicists, isbn=9780931830617, http://www.seg.org/documents/10161/77915/seg_mt_emap_1987.pdf</eadetcit>
		</overview>
	</eainfo>
	<distinfo>
		<distrib>
			<cntinfo>
				<cntorgp>
					<cntorg>U.S. Geological Survey - ScienceBase</cntorg>
					<cntper>U.S. Geological Survey - ScienceBase</cntper>
				</cntorgp>
				<cntaddr>
					<addrtype>mailing and physical</addrtype>
					<address>Denver Federal Center, Building 810, Mail Stop 302</address>
					<city>Denver</city>
					<state>CO</state>
					<postal>80225</postal>
					<country>USA</country>
				</cntaddr>
				<cntvoice>1-888-275-8747</cntvoice>
				<cntemail>sciencebase@usgs.gov</cntemail>
			</cntinfo>
		</distrib>
		<distliab>Digital_Transfer_Option Online_Option</distliab>
	</distinfo>
	<metainfo>
		<metd>20171128</metd>
		<metc>
			<cntinfo>
				<cntperp>
					<cntper>Philip Brown</cntper>
					<cntorg>U.S. Geological Survey</cntorg>
				</cntperp>
				<cntpos>Geophysicist</cntpos>
				<cntaddr>
					<addrtype>Physical</addrtype>
					<address>Mail Stop 964, West 6th Ave. and Kipling St., DFC Bldg. 20</address>
					<city>Denver</city>
					<state>CO</state>
					<postal>80225-0046</postal>
					<country>US</country>
				</cntaddr>
				<cntvoice>303-236-1310</cntvoice>
				<cntemail>pbrown@usgs.gov</cntemail>
				<cntinst>Additional information about metadata creator: Brown, P.J., http://orcid.org/0000-0002-2415-7462</cntinst>
			</cntinfo>
		</metc>
		<metstdn>FGDC Content Standard for Digital Geospatial Metadata</metstdn>
		<metstdv>FGDC-STD-001-1998</metstdv>
	</metainfo>
</metadata>
