<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<metadata>
	<idinfo>
		<citation>
			<citeinfo>
				<origin>Reitman, J.</origin>
				<origin>Rodriguez, B. D.</origin>
				<origin>Brown, P. J.</origin>								
				<pubdate>2019</pubdate>
				<title>{title}</title>
				<edition>1</edition>
				<geoform>ASCII and Binary Digital Data</geoform>
				<pubinfo>
					<pubplace>Denver, CO</pubplace>
					<publish>U.S. Geological Survey</publish>
				</pubinfo>
				<othercit>Additional information about Originators:Reitman, J., http://orcid.org/0000-0003-3551-9884;Rodriguez, B.D., http://orcid.org/0000-0002-2263-611X; Brown, P.J., http://orcid.org/0000-0002-2415-7462</othercit>
				<onlink>https://doi.org/10.5066/P9CIAXC5</onlink>
			</citeinfo>
		</citation>
		<descript>
			<abstract>This dataset includes audiomagnetotelluric (AMT) sounding data collected in July 2018 in the Silverton Caldera complex, Colorado, in the Southern Rocky Mountain Volcanic Field, by the U.S. Geological Survey (USGS). Along with geologic mapping, airborne magnetics, airborne electromagnetics, and magnetotellurics, the USGS collected AMT data at 24 sites along four profiles ranging from 3 to 6 kilometers in length across the north-western structural margin of the Silverton caldera in Mineral Basin, across the south-eastern margin of the caldera along Cunningham Creek, within the caldera in Eureka Graben, and within the caldera along upper Cement Creek near the Gold King mine.</abstract>
			<purpose>The purpose of this data release is to provide audiomagnetotelluric (AMT) station locations and data to the public. The purpose of the survey is to help to characterize subsurface rock properties important for understanding surface water and groundwater quality issues, and also to improve knowledge of deep geologic structures that may have been conduits for hydrothermal fluids that formed mineral deposits. The study also has general applications to mineral resource assessments in other areas of the world, and to identifying possible groundwater flow paths and associated geochemistry important in abandoned mine lands cleanup.</purpose>
			<supplinf>
				This data product contains MT transfer functions (TFs), which define the frequency-dependent linear relations between components of electromagnetic (EM) field variations measured at a single site. Two sorts of TF are provided for most sites. All TFs provide input data for subsequent MT inversion and interpretation. They are estimated from the raw EM time series by (a) Fourier transforming data in a series of short overlapping time windows, and (b) applying robust regression methods to the resulting sequence of Fourier coefficients. For remote reference estimates data from a second site are used for noise cancellation, and to reduce bias due to noise in the predicting magnetic channels. Apparent resistivities and phases, which can be computed from the off-diagonal components of the impedance tensors, are frequently used in 2-dimensional (2D) interpretations. The EMTF data product includes estimates of the TFs for a range of periods (which may vary, depending on instrumentation and deployment time), as well as estimation error covariances.
				For more information on the EDI data format:
				Wight, David E., 1988, MT/EMAP Data Interchange Standard, Revision 1.0: Society of Exploration Geophysicists technical standards committee report, 77 p, isbn = 9780931830617, http://www.seg.org/documents/10161/77915/seg_mt_emap_1987.pdf. This report can be downloaded for free from the Society of Exploration Geophysics (SEG) Technical Standards website, http://seg.org/Publications/SEG-Technical-Standards. These metadata document the full suite of MT data for this site and includes the files below. Their contents are described in the entity and attribute section of the metadata.
 {BeginFileListingHere}
				</supplinf>
		</descript>
		<timeperd>
			<timeinfo>
				<rngdates>
					<begdate>{begdate}</begdate>
					<enddate>{enddate}</enddate>
				</rngdates>
			</timeinfo>
			<current>ground condition</current>
		</timeperd>
		<status>
			<progress>Complete</progress>
			<update>Not planned</update>
		</status>
		<spdom>
			<bounding>
				<westbc>{SiteLon}</westbc>
				<eastbc>{SiteLon}</eastbc>
				<northbc>{SiteLat}</northbc>
				<southbc>{SiteLat}</southbc>
			</bounding>
		</spdom>
 {keywords}
		<accconst>Please see 'Distribution Info' for details.</accconst>
		<useconst>There is no guarantee concerning the accuracy of the data. Any user who modifies the data is obligated to describe the types of modifications they perform. Data have been checked to ensure the accuracy. If any errors are detected, please notify the originating office. The U.S. Geological Survey strongly recommends that careful attention be paid to the metadata file associated with these data. Acknowledgment of the U.S. Geological Survey would be appreciated in products derived from these data. User specifically agrees not to misrepresent the data, nor to imply that changes made were approved or endorsed by the U.S. Geological Survey. Please refer to https://www2.usgs.gov/laws/privacy.html for the USGS disclaimer.</useconst>
		<ptcontac>
			<cntinfo>
				<cntorgp>
					<cntorg>USGS - Crustal Geology, Geophysics, and Geochemistry Science Center</cntorg>
					<cntper>Brian D. Rodriguez</cntper>
				</cntorgp>
				<cntpos>Research Geophysicist</cntpos>
				<cntaddr>
					<addrtype>Physical</addrtype>
					<address>Mail Stop 964, West 6th Ave. and Kipling St., DFC Bldg. 20</address>
					<city>Denver</city>
					<state>CO</state>
					<postal>80225-0046</postal>
					<country>US</country>
				</cntaddr>
				<cntvoice>303-236-1361</cntvoice>
				<cntemail>brod@usgs.gov</cntemail>
			</cntinfo>
		</ptcontac>
		<datacred>Data collected by Brian D. Rodriguez of the Geology, Geophysics, and Geochemistry Science Center. This project was funded by U.S. Geological Survey (USGS) Minerals Resources Program (MRP), in cooperation with the U.S. Bureau of Land Management (BLM)and U.S. Forest Service (USFS).</datacred>
		<native>MS-DOS version 6.22</native>
	</idinfo>
	<dataqual>
		<attracc>
			<attraccr>MS-DOS version 6.22</attraccr>
		</attracc>
		<logic>Data set is considered complete for the information presented, as described in the abstract. Users are advised to read the rest of the metadata record carefully for additional details.</logic>
		<complete>Data set is considered complete for the information presented, as described in the abstract. Users are advised to read the rest of the metadata record carefully for additional details.</complete>
		<posacc>
			<horizpa>
				<horizpar>Spatial locations were determined from hand-held global positioning system (GPS) devices. In general, the GPS units used by field scientists recorded sample locations to within 100 feet (30 meters) of the true location. The locations were verified using a geographic information system (GIS) and digital topographic maps.</horizpar>
			</horizpa>
			<vertacc>
				<vertaccr>Elevations were determined from USGS, The National Map, Bulk Point Query Service based on the USGS 3DEP (3D elevation program) 1/3 arc-second layer (10-meter). Vertical accuracy was not assessed for this specific dataset. The overall absolute vertical accuracy of the seamless DEMs within the conterminous United States (2013), expressed as the root mean square error (RMSE) of 25,310 reference points, was 1.55 meters (USGS, 2014 -  http://dx.doi.org/10.3133/ofr20141008). The vertical accuracy varies across the U.S. as a result of differences in source DEM quality, terrain relief, land cover, and other factors.</vertaccr>
			</vertacc>
		</posacc>
		<lineage>
			<procstep>
	        	<procdesc>Multiple high frequency time series (TS1 file extension), Fourier Coefficient (FC6, FC7, FC8, FC9 file extension), and Synchronous Detection Mode spectra cross power blocks (SD6, SD7, SD8, and SD9 file extensions) were each recorded for about 1 minute with an Electromagnetic Instruments (EMI) MT-1 MT data acquisition instrument employing orthogonal horizontal EMI AMT induction magnetic coils and EMI Titanium electrodes, along with a vertical EMI AMT induction magnetic coil. The proprietary, DOS-based, EMI recording software used is MTACQ, version 2.00 (September 17, 2004). The collected time series were stored on a portable field-rugged laptop computer and then converted to intermediate spectra cross power files (BP1 file extension) using fast Fourier transform (FFT) techniques and least-squares, cross-spectral analysis to solve for a tensor transfer function. Remote reference stations were not used because manmade noise sources were assumed to be minimal in this remote area. The time series and spectra cross power files were downloaded from the portable laptop each evening for further processing. The time series files are readable by other third-party software, such as Geosystem's WinGLink, version 2.20.02 (June 5, 2008), but the Fourier Coefficient and cross power files are only known to be readable by the EMI proprietary software.</procdesc>
				<procdate>{CollectionDate}</procdate>
			</procstep>
			<procstep>
				<procdesc>Combine multiple frequency band BP and SD cross power files into a single cross power file (AVG file extension) using EMI's MTACQ, version 2.00, software</procdesc>
				<procdate>{CombinationDate}</procdate>
			</procstep>
			<procstep>
				<procdesc>Convert cross power AVG file to spectra edi file using EMI's MTACQ, version 2.00, software</procdesc>
				<procdate>{ConversionDate}</procdate>
			</procstep>
			<procstep>
				<procdesc>Rotate data to geographic north and convert spectra edi file to a Transfer Function dump file using the proprietary, Windows-based, Geotools' GeotoolsMT, version 7.30 (May 28, 1998), software</procdesc>
				<procdate>{RotationDate}</procdate>
			</procstep>
			<procstep>
				<procdesc>Mine metadata from AVG, spectra edi, and dump files to create a Transfer Function edi file</procdesc>
				<procdate>{HarvestDate}</procdate>
	</procstep>		</lineage>
	</dataqual>
	<spdoinfo>
		<direct>Point</direct>
		<ptvctinf>
			<sdtsterm>
				<sdtstype>Entity point</sdtstype>
				<ptvctcnt>1</ptvctcnt>
			</sdtsterm>
		</ptvctinf>
	</spdoinfo>
	<spref>
		<horizsys>
			<geograph>
				<latres>0.0196481178</latres>
				<longres>0.0409100603</longres>
				<geogunit>Decimal degrees</geogunit>
			</geograph>
			<geodetic>
				<horizdn>NAD27 CONUS</horizdn>
				<ellips>Clarke 1866</ellips>
				<semiaxis>6378206.4</semiaxis>
				<denflat>294.9786982</denflat>
			</geodetic>
		</horizsys>
	</spref>
	<eainfo>
		<detailed>
			<enttyp>
				<enttypl>Text File {EdiFileName}</enttypl>
				<enttypd>Transfer Function EDI File</enttypd>
				<enttypds>U.S. Geological Survey</enttypds>
			</enttyp>
			<attr>
				<attrlabl>FREQ</attrlabl>
				<attrdef>Data block containing a set of frequencies in hertz (Hz.) It defines the frequency set for succeeding data within that data section which are functions of frequency.</attrdef>
				<attrdefs>U.S. Geological Survey</attrdefs>
				<attrdomv>
				<rdom>
				<rdommin>{frequencyMax}</rdommin>
				<rdommax>{frequencyMin}</rdommax>
				<attrunit>Hertz</attrunit>
			</rdom>
			</attrdomv>
			</attr>
			<attr>
				<attrlabl>ZROT</attrlabl>
				<attrdef>Data block containing a set of rotation angles in degrees used for impedances.</attrdef>
				<attrdefs>U.S. Geological Survey</attrdefs>
				<attrdomv>
				<rdom>
				<rdommin>{rotationMin}</rdommin>
				<rdommax>{rotationMax}</rdommax>
				<attrunit>Degrees</attrunit>
				</rdom>
				</attrdomv>
			</attr>
			{ImpedanceAttributes}
			{TipperAttributes}
			<attr>
				<attrlabl>RHOROT</attrlabl>
				<attrdef>Data block containing a set of rotation angles in degrees used for apparent resistivities.</attrdef>
				<attrdefs>U.S. Geological Survey</attrdefs>
				<attrdomv>
					<rdom>
				<rdommin>{RHOROTmin}</rdommin>
				<rdommax>{RHOROTmax}</rdommax>
				<attrunit>Degrees</attrunit>
				</rdom>
				</attrdomv>
			</attr>
			<attr>
				<attrlabl>RHOXX</attrlabl>
				<attrdef>Magnitude of apparent resistivity (ohm-m) computed from Zxx</attrdef>
				<attrdefs>U.S. Geological Survey</attrdefs>
				<attrdomv>
					<rdom>
				<rdommin>{RHOXXmin}</rdommin>
				<rdommax>{RHOXXmax}</rdommax>
				<attrunit>ohm-m</attrunit>
				</rdom>
				</attrdomv>
			</attr>
			<attr>
				<attrlabl>PHSXX</attrlabl>
				<attrdef>Phase angle of apparent resistivity (deg) computed from Zxx</attrdef>
				<attrdefs>U.S. Geological Survey</attrdefs>
				<attrdomv>
					<rdom>
				<rdommin>{PHSXXmin}</rdommin>
				<rdommax>{PHSXXmax}</rdommax>
				<attrunit>Degrees</attrunit>
				</rdom>
				</attrdomv>
			</attr>
			<attr>
				<attrlabl>RHOXX.ERR</attrlabl>
				<attrdef>Log10 error bar (in decades) associated with Rhoxx</attrdef>
				<attrdefs>U.S. Geological Survey</attrdefs>
				<attrdomv>
					<rdom>
				<rdommin>{RHOXXERRmin}</rdommin>
				<rdommax>{RHOXXERRmax}</rdommax>
				<attrunit>Log10 ohm-m</attrunit>
				</rdom>
				</attrdomv>
			</attr>
			<attr>
				<attrlabl>PHSXX.ERR</attrlabl>
				<attrdef>Error bar (in degrees) associated with  Phsxx</attrdef>
				<attrdefs>U.S. Geological Survey</attrdefs>
				<attrdomv>
					<rdom>
				<rdommin>{PHSXXERRmin}</rdommin>
				<rdommax>{PHSXXERRmax}</rdommax>
				<attrunit>Degrees</attrunit>
				</rdom>
				</attrdomv>
			</attr>
			<attr>
				<attrlabl>RHOXY</attrlabl>
				<attrdef>Magnitude of apparent resistivity (ohm-m) computed from Zxy</attrdef>
				<attrdefs>U.S. Geological Survey</attrdefs>
				<attrdomv>
					<rdom>
				<rdommin>{RHOXYmin}</rdommin>
				<rdommax>{RHOXYmax}</rdommax>
				<attrunit>ohm-m</attrunit>
				</rdom>
				</attrdomv>
			</attr>
			<attr>
				<attrlabl>PHSXY</attrlabl>
				<attrdef>Phase angle of apparent resistivity (deg) computed from Zxy</attrdef>
				<attrdefs>U.S. Geological Survey</attrdefs>
				<attrdomv>
					<rdom>
				<rdommin>{PHSXYmin}</rdommin>
				<rdommax>{PHSXYmax}</rdommax>
				<attrunit>Degrees</attrunit>
				</rdom>
				</attrdomv>
			</attr>
			<attr>
				<attrlabl>RHOXY.ERR</attrlabl>
				<attrdef>Log10 error bar (in decades) associated with Rhoxy</attrdef>
				<attrdefs>U.S. Geological Survey</attrdefs>
				<attrdomv>
					<rdom>
				<rdommin>{RHOXYERRmin}</rdommin>
				<rdommax>{RHOXYERRmax}</rdommax>
				<attrunit>Log10 ohm-m</attrunit>
				</rdom>
				</attrdomv>
			</attr>
			<attr>
				<attrlabl>PHSXY.ERR</attrlabl>
				<attrdef>Error bar (in degrees) associated with  Phsxy</attrdef>
				<attrdefs>U.S. Geological Survey</attrdefs>
				<attrdomv>
					<rdom>
				<rdommin>{PHSXYERRmin}</rdommin>
				<rdommax>{PHSXYERRmax}</rdommax>
				<attrunit>Degrees</attrunit>
				</rdom>
				</attrdomv>
			</attr>
			<attr>
				<attrlabl>RHOYX</attrlabl>
				<attrdef>Magnitude of apparent resistivity (ohm-m) computed from Zyx</attrdef>
				<attrdefs>U.S. Geological Survey</attrdefs>
				<attrdomv>
					<rdom>
				<rdommin>{RHOYXmin}</rdommin>
				<rdommax>{RHOYXmax}</rdommax>
				<attrunit>ohm-m</attrunit>
				</rdom>
				</attrdomv>
			</attr>
			<attr>
				<attrlabl>PHSYX</attrlabl>
				<attrdef>Phase angle of apparent resistivity (deg) computed from Zyx</attrdef>
				<attrdefs>U.S. Geological Survey</attrdefs>
				<attrdomv>
					<rdom>
				<rdommin>{PHSYXmin}</rdommin>
				<rdommax>{PHSYXmax}</rdommax>
				<attrunit>Degrees</attrunit>
				</rdom>
				</attrdomv>
			</attr>
			<attr>
				<attrlabl>RHOYX.ERR</attrlabl>
				<attrdef>Log10 error bar (in decades) associated with Rhoyx</attrdef>
				<attrdefs>U.S. Geological Survey</attrdefs>
				<attrdomv>
					<rdom>
				<rdommin>{RHOYXERRmin}</rdommin>
				<rdommax>{RHOYXERRmax}</rdommax>
				<attrunit>Log10 ohm-m</attrunit>
				</rdom>
				</attrdomv>
			</attr>
			<attr>
				<attrlabl>PHSYX.ERR</attrlabl>
				<attrdef>Error bar (in degrees) associated with  Phsyx</attrdef>
				<attrdefs>U.S. Geological Survey</attrdefs>
				<attrdomv>
					<rdom>
				<rdommin>{PHSYXERRmin}</rdommin>
				<rdommax>{PHSYXERRmax}</rdommax>
				<attrunit>Degrees</attrunit>
				</rdom>
				</attrdomv>
			</attr>
			<attr>
				<attrlabl>RHOYY</attrlabl>
				<attrdef>Magnitude of apparent resistivity (ohm-m) computed from Zyy</attrdef>
				<attrdefs>U.S. Geological Survey</attrdefs>
				<attrdomv>
					<rdom>
				<rdommin>{RHOYYmin}</rdommin>
				<rdommax>{RHOYYmax}</rdommax>
				<attrunit>ohm-m</attrunit>
				</rdom>
				</attrdomv>
			</attr>
			<attr>
				<attrlabl>PHSYY</attrlabl>
				<attrdef>Phase angle of apparent resistivity (deg) computed from Zyy</attrdef>
				<attrdefs>U.S. Geological Survey</attrdefs>
				<attrdomv>
					<rdom>
				<rdommin>{PHSYYmin}</rdommin>
				<rdommax>{PHSYYmax}</rdommax>
				<attrunit>Degrees</attrunit>
				</rdom>
				</attrdomv>
			</attr>
			<attr>
				<attrlabl>RHOYY.ERR</attrlabl>
				<attrdef>Log10 error bar (in decades) associated with Rhoyy</attrdef>
				<attrdefs>U.S. Geological Survey</attrdefs>
				<attrdomv>
					<rdom>
				<rdommin>{RHOYYERRmin}</rdommin>
				<rdommax>{RHOYYERRmax}</rdommax>
				<attrunit>Log10 ohm-m</attrunit>
				</rdom>
				</attrdomv>
			</attr>
			<attr>
				<attrlabl>PHSYY.ERR</attrlabl>
				<attrdef>Error bar (in degrees) associated with  Phsyy</attrdef>
				<attrdefs>U.S. Geological Survey</attrdefs>
				<attrdomv>
					<rdom>
				<rdommin>{PHSYYERRmin}</rdommin>
				<rdommax>{PHSYYERRmax}</rdommax>
				<attrunit>Degrees</attrunit>
				</rdom>
				</attrdomv>
			</attr>
			<attr>
				<attrlabl>TIPMAG</attrlabl>
				<attrdef>Magnitude of total tipper</attrdef>
				<attrdefs>U.S. Geological Survey</attrdefs>
				<attrdomv>
					<rdom>
				<rdommin>{TIPMAGmin}</rdommin>
				<rdommax>{TIPMAGmax}</rdommax>
				<attrunit>Unitless</attrunit>
				</rdom>
				</attrdomv>
			</attr>
			<attr>
				<attrlabl>TIPPHS</attrlabl>
				<attrdef>Phase angle (deg) of total tipper</attrdef>
				<attrdefs>U.S. Geological Survey</attrdefs>
				<attrdomv>
					<rdom>
				<rdommin>{TIPPHSmin}</rdommin>
				<rdommax>{TIPPHSmax}</rdommax>
				<attrunit>Degrees</attrunit>
				</rdom>
				</attrdomv>
			</attr>
			<attr>
				<attrlabl>TIPMAG.ERR</attrlabl>
				<attrdef>Error bar associated with TIPMAG</attrdef>
				<attrdefs>U.S. Geological Survey</attrdefs>
				<attrdomv>
					<rdom>
				<rdommin>{TIPMAGERRmin}</rdommin>
				<rdommax>{TIPMAGERRmax}</rdommax>
				<attrunit>Unitless</attrunit>
				</rdom>
				</attrdomv>
			</attr>
			<attr>
				<attrlabl>TIPPHS.ERR</attrlabl>
				<attrdef>Error bar (in degrees) associated with TIPPHS</attrdef>
				<attrdefs>U.S. Geological Survey</attrdefs>
				<attrdomv>
					<rdom>
				<rdommin>{TIPPHSERRmin}</rdommin>
				<rdommax>{TIPPHSERRmax}</rdommax>
				<attrunit>Degrees</attrunit>
				</rdom>
				</attrdomv>
			</attr>
			<attr>
				<attrlabl>ZSTRIKE</attrlabl>
				<attrdef>Impedance strike angle (deg) computed from the impedance tensor Z</attrdef>
				<attrdefs>U.S. Geological Survey</attrdefs>
				<attrdomv>
					<rdom>
				<rdommin>{ZSTRIKEmin}</rdommin>
				<rdommax>{ZSTRIKEmax}</rdommax>
				<attrunit>Degrees</attrunit>
				</rdom>
				</attrdomv>
			</attr>
			<attr>
				<attrlabl>ZSKEW</attrlabl>
				<attrdef>Impedance skew computed from the impedance tensor Z</attrdef>
				<attrdefs>U.S. Geological Survey</attrdefs>
				<attrdomv>
					<rdom>
				<rdommin>{ZSKEWmin}</rdommin>
				<rdommax>{ZSKEWmax}</rdommax>
				<attrunit>Unitless</attrunit>
				</rdom>
				</attrdomv>
			</attr>
			<attr>
				<attrlabl>TSTRIKE</attrlabl>
				<attrdef>Tipper strike angle (deg) computed from the tipper tensor T</attrdef>
				<attrdefs>U.S. Geological Survey</attrdefs>
				<attrdomv>
					<rdom>
				<rdommin>{TSTRIKEmin}</rdommin>
				<rdommax>{TSTRIKEmax}</rdommax>
				<attrunit>Degrees</attrunit>
				</rdom>
				</attrdomv>
			</attr>
			<attr>
				<attrlabl>COH MEAS1=1011.001  MEAS2=1015.001</attrlabl>
				<attrdef>Ordinary coherency between any two measurements as a function of freq.</attrdef>
				<attrdefs>U.S. Geological Survey</attrdefs>
				<attrdomv>
					<rdom>
				<rdommin>{COH1min}</rdommin>
				<rdommax>{COH1max}</rdommax>
				<attrunit>Unitless</attrunit>
				</rdom>
				</attrdomv>
			</attr>
			<attr>
				<attrlabl>COH MEAS1=1012.001  MEAS2=1014.001</attrlabl>
				<attrdef>Ordinary coherency between any two measurements as a function of freq.</attrdef>
				<attrdefs>U.S. Geological Survey</attrdefs>
				<attrdomv>
					<rdom>
				<rdommin>{COH2min}</rdommin>
				<rdommax>{COH2max}</rdommax>
				<attrunit>Unitless</attrunit>
				</rdom>
				</attrdomv>
			</attr>
			<attr>
				<attrlabl>COH MEAS1=1011.001  MEAS2=1014.001</attrlabl>
				<attrdef>Ordinary coherency between any two measurements as a function of freq.</attrdef>
				<attrdefs>U.S. Geological Survey</attrdefs>
				<attrdomv>
					<rdom>
				<rdommin>{COH3min}</rdommin>
				<rdommax>{COH3max}</rdommax>
				<attrunit>Unitless</attrunit>
				</rdom>
				</attrdomv>
			</attr>
			<attr>
				<attrlabl>COH MEAS1=1012.001  MEAS2=1015.001</attrlabl>
				<attrdef>Ordinary coherency between any two measurements as a function of freq.</attrdef>
				<attrdefs>U.S. Geological Survey</attrdefs>
				<attrdomv>
					<rdom>
				<rdommin>{COH4min}</rdommin>
				<rdommax>{COH4max}</rdommax>
				<attrunit>Unitless</attrunit>
				</rdom>
				</attrdomv>
			</attr>
			<attr>
				<attrlabl>EPREDCOH  MEAS1=1011.001  MEAS2=1012.001  EPRED= 1014.001</attrlabl>
				<attrdef>Multiple coherency relationship between an E measurement, and a predicted E measurement derived from two H measurements and a tensor impedance Z.</attrdef>
				<attrdefs>U.S. Geological Survey</attrdefs>
				<attrdomv>
					<rdom>
				<rdommin>{EPREDCOH1min}</rdommin>
				<rdommax>{EPREDCOH1max}</rdommax>
				<attrunit>Unitless</attrunit>
				</rdom>
				</attrdomv>
			</attr>
			<attr>
				<attrlabl>EPREDCOH  MEAS1=1011.001  MEAS2=1012.001  EPRED= 1015.001</attrlabl>
				<attrdef>Multiple coherency relationship between an E measurement, and a predicted E measurement derived from two H measurements and a tensor impedance Z.</attrdef>
				<attrdefs>U.S. Geological Survey</attrdefs>
				<attrdomv>
					<rdom>
				<rdommin>{EPREDCOH2min}</rdommin>
				<rdommax>{EPREDCOH2max}</rdommax>
				<attrunit>Unitless</attrunit>
				</rdom>
				</attrdomv>
			</attr>
			<attr>
				<attrlabl>SIGAMP  MEAS=1011</attrlabl>
				<attrdef>Signal amplitude (or power) spectra for a measurement as a function of frequency.</attrdef>
				<attrdefs>U.S. Geological Survey</attrdefs>
				<attrdomv>
					<rdom>
				<rdommin>{SIGAMP1min}</rdommin>
				<rdommax>{SIGAMP1max}</rdommax>
				<attrunit>gammas/SQRT(Hertz)</attrunit>
				</rdom>
				</attrdomv>
			</attr>
			<attr>
				<attrlabl>SIGAMP  MEAS=1012</attrlabl>
				<attrdef>Signal amplitude (or power) spectra for a measurement as a function of frequency.</attrdef>
				<attrdefs>U.S. Geological Survey</attrdefs>
				<attrdomv>
					<rdom>
				<rdommin>{SIGAMP2min}</rdommin>
				<rdommax>{SIGAMP2max}</rdommax>
				<attrunit>gammas/SQRT(Hertz)</attrunit>
				</rdom>
				</attrdomv>
			</attr>
			<attr>
				<attrlabl>SIGAMP  MEAS=1013</attrlabl>
				<attrdef>Signal amplitude (or power) spectra for a measurement as a function of frequency.</attrdef>
				<attrdefs>U.S. Geological Survey</attrdefs>
				<attrdomv>
					<rdom>
				<rdommin>{SIGAMP3min}</rdommin>
				<rdommax>{SIGAMP3max}</rdommax>
				<attrunit>gammas/SQRT(Hertz)</attrunit>
				</rdom>
				</attrdomv>
			</attr>
			<attr>
				<attrlabl>SIGAMP  MEAS=1014</attrlabl>
				<attrdef>Signal amplitude (or power) spectra for a measurement as a function of frequency.</attrdef>
				<attrdefs>U.S. Geological Survey</attrdefs>
				<attrdomv>
					<rdom>
				<rdommin>{SIGAMP4min}</rdommin>
				<rdommax>{SIGAMP4max}</rdommax>
				<attrunit>mV/Km/SQRT(Hertz)</attrunit>
				</rdom>
				</attrdomv>
			</attr>
			<attr>
				<attrlabl>SIGAMP  MEAS=1015</attrlabl>
				<attrdef>Signal amplitude (or power) spectra for a measurement as a function of frequency.</attrdef>
				<attrdefs>U.S. Geological Survey</attrdefs>
				<attrdomv>
					<rdom>
				<rdommin>{SIGAMP5min}</rdommin>
				<rdommax>{SIGAMP5max}</rdommax>
				<attrunit>mV/Km/SQRT(Hertz)</attrunit>
				</rdom>
				</attrdomv>
			</attr>
			<attr>
				<attrlabl>SIGNOISE</attrlabl>
				<attrdef>Signal-to-noise ratio for a measurement as a function of frequency.</attrdef>
				<attrdefs>U.S. Geological Survey</attrdefs>
				<attrdomv>
					<rdom>
				<rdommin>{SIGNOISE1min}</rdommin>
				<rdommax>{SIGNOISE1max}</rdommax>
				<attrunit>Unitless</attrunit>
				</rdom>
				</attrdomv>
			</attr>
			<attr>
				<attrlabl>SIGNOISE</attrlabl>
				<attrdef>Signal-to-noise ratio for a measurement as a function of frequency.</attrdef>
				<attrdefs>U.S. Geological Survey</attrdefs>
				<attrdomv>
					<rdom>
				<rdommin>{SIGNOISE2min}</rdommin>
				<rdommax>{SIGNOISE2max}</rdommax>
				<attrunit>Unitless</attrunit>
				</rdom>
				</attrdomv>
			</attr>
			<attr>
				<attrlabl>SIGNOISE</attrlabl>
				<attrdef>Signal-to-noise ratio for a measurement as a function of frequency.</attrdef>
				<attrdefs>U.S. Geological Survey</attrdefs>
				<attrdomv>
					<rdom>
				<rdommin>{SIGNOISE3min}</rdommin>
				<rdommax>{SIGNOISE3max}</rdommax>
				<attrunit>Unitless</attrunit>
				</rdom>
				</attrdomv>
			</attr>
			<attr>
				<attrlabl>SIGNOISE</attrlabl>
				<attrdef>Signal-to-noise ratio for a measurement as a function of frequency.</attrdef>
				<attrdefs>U.S. Geological Survey</attrdefs>
				<attrdomv>
					<rdom>
				<rdommin>{SIGNOISE4min}</rdommin>
				<rdommax>{SIGNOISE4max}</rdommax>
				<attrunit>Unitless</attrunit>
				</rdom>
				</attrdomv>
			</attr>
			<attr>
				<attrlabl>SIGNOISE</attrlabl>
				<attrdef>Signal-to-noise ratio for a measurement as a function of frequency.</attrdef>
				<attrdefs>U.S. Geological Survey</attrdefs>
				<attrdomv>
					<rdom>
				<rdommin>{SIGNOISE5min}</rdommin>
				<rdommax>{SIGNOISE5max}</rdommax>
				<attrunit>Unitless</attrunit>
				</rdom>
				</attrdomv>
			</attr>
		</detailed>
	{EandA}
		<overview>
			<eaover>MT/EMAP Data Interchange Standard, Revision 1.0, Dec 1987, David E. Wight. This standard was never published in Geophysics.</eaover>
			<eadetcit>For more information on the EDI data format: Wight, D.E., 1988, MT/EMAP Data Interchange Standard, Technical standards committee report, Society of Exploration Geophysicists, isbn=9780931830617, http://www.seg.org/documents/10161/77915/seg_mt_emap_1987.pdf</eadetcit>
		</overview>
	</eainfo>
	<distinfo>
		<distrib>
			<cntinfo>
				<cntorgp>
					<cntorg>U.S. Geological Survey - ScienceBase</cntorg>
					<cntper>U.S. Geological Survey - ScienceBase</cntper>
				</cntorgp>
				<cntaddr>
					<addrtype>mailing and physical</addrtype>
					<address>Denver Federal Center, Building 810, Mail Stop 302</address>
					<city>Denver</city>
					<state>CO</state>
					<postal>80225</postal>
					<country>USA</country>
				</cntaddr>
				<cntvoice>1-888-275-8747</cntvoice>
				<cntemail>sciencebase@usgs.gov</cntemail>
			</cntinfo>
		</distrib>
		<distliab>Digital_Transfer_Option Online_Option</distliab>
	</distinfo>
	<metainfo>
		<metd>20171128</metd>
		<metc>
			<cntinfo>
				<cntperp>
					<cntper>Philip Brown</cntper>
					<cntorg>U.S. Geological Survey</cntorg>
				</cntperp>
				<cntpos>Geophysicist</cntpos>
				<cntaddr>
					<addrtype>Physical</addrtype>
					<address>Mail Stop 964, West 6th Ave. and Kipling St., DFC Bldg. 20</address>
					<city>Denver</city>
					<state>CO</state>
					<postal>80225-0046</postal>
					<country>US</country>
				</cntaddr>
				<cntvoice>303-236-1310</cntvoice>
				<cntemail>pbrown@usgs.gov</cntemail>
				<cntinst>Additional information about metadata creator: Brown, P.J., http://orcid.org/0000-0002-2415-7462</cntinst>
			</cntinfo>
		</metc>
		<metstdn>FGDC Content Standard for Digital Geospatial Metadata</metstdn>
		<metstdv>FGDC-STD-001-1998</metstdv>
	</metainfo>
</metadata>